vecto2000.com 2017-11-20

# PRIVACY POLICY - Vecto2000.com

VECTO2000.com is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement discloses the privacy practices for VECTO2000.com. Within this Privacy statement you can find details on how we collect and use, and under which circumstances may share your information. If you have any questions about our privacy statement, please email us.

### General Information

We collect the names and e-mail addresses of people who communicate with us by e-mail, nor When you engage in certain activities on the Website, such as creating an account, subscribing to our newsletters, posting a comment, submitting content, filling out our contact, etc.

Personally Identifiable Information We collect information only to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, our product offerings, and to tailor your experience to the best.

We collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve our sites, to process your transactions, to provide customer service. We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send transaction-related communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, and purchase confirmations. We may also send you surveys or marketing emails to inform you of new products or services or other information that may be of interest. If you do not wish to receive marketing emails, you may follow the “unsubscribe” instructions included within each email communication.

Personal information are not shared with or sold to any other party, except that we may release information in the following cases:

  1. We may share your personal information within our corporate group, including with our subsidiaries, all of whom may use your information for the purposes disclosed herein.
  2. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process or a court order, enforce or apply this Privacy Statement, our Website Terms of Use or other agreements, or protect the rights, property or safety of the Website, its Users or others.
  3. Information about our customers, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, or sale of the company, in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company. We will notify you by email or by putting a notice on our web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Use of Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard drive or device. We use cookies to save you time while using the Website, for analytics, remind us who you are, track and target your session and store the contents of your shopping cart in order to provide a customized experience. Cookies contain information, including personal information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. The information that cookies collect includes the date and time of your visit, your registration information, and your navigational and purchase history.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify our Privacy Policy at any time. If we make significant changes to our Privacy Policy which would affect the way we collect and use any of your personal information, we will revise the “last updated” date at the top of the policy. we will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such changes here or on our home page, or by sending you an email. We encourage you to review this policy whenever you visit one of our sites.

### Contact Information

Any questions you may have about our Privacy Policy should be addressed to  
info@VECTO2000.com
